▍2026 美网 女单第三轮
郑钦文 1-6 7-6³ 7-5 凯斯 · 赛后新闻发布会
tough one today.
今天这场不好打
Can you just take us
能不能带我们
through your perspective?
从你的角度回顾一下？
What was what was going on maybe
第三盘那会儿
in your mind in the third set?
你脑子里在想什么？
Yeah.
嗯
I mean, I feel like I obviously got off
我觉得我开局
to a really good lead and then I just
拿到了很大的领先
got really I mean got really scared,
然后我就变得非常害怕
but like I couldn't swing.
就是挥不开拍了
I don't know.
我不知道
Tennis just feels really hard right now.
网球现在感觉真的很难
So feel like that kind of took over,
感觉那种情绪占了上风
right?
好
She said when it was five love,
她说 5-0 的时候
she didn't feel like she was playing that bad.
她不觉得自己打得有多差
She thought you were playing that well.
她觉得是你打得太好了
Did you feel like your level dropped at all
你觉得是你的水平掉了
or hers really came up that much?
还是她真的提升了那么多？
I mean I think my level dropped
我觉得是我的水平掉了
and she started to play better.
然后她开始打得更好
Yeah.
对
David,
大卫
how are you feeling coming
来打这站的时候
into the tournament
你的感觉是怎么样
when you say tennis was is hard right now?
你说网球现在很难
has this been how you've been feeling
这种感觉是持续了
for a few months, a few weeks or just
几个月 几周 还是……
Yeah, I mean I just feel like I've kind
嗯 我觉得我
of been struggling for a while now
已经挣扎了有一阵子了
and I feel like I've was able to kind
我觉得之前还能
of play through it for a bit.
硬撑着打过去
I'm sure everyone could kind of see
我相信大家都看得出来
that I was struggling a little bit,
我有点挣扎
but inside it's felt probably even bigger
但在心里 这件事
than that.
可能比看上去还要大
And yeah, it just some weeks are easier
有些星期会好过一点
than others and this week is obviously one
而这一周显然是
of the harder ones just cuz you care
比较难熬的那一周
so much.
因为你太在乎了
And yeah, I'm going
所以我想
to have to make some sort of changes.
我得做出一些改变
What?
嗯？
I I got in late.
我来晚了
I apologize.
不好意思
But Madison,
麦迪逊
what were the specifics do you think
你觉得具体是什么
of what turned the match around?
让这场球翻了过来？
Like at the end,
到最后
I think she started playing better.
我觉得她开始打得更好
I started playing poorly and then I felt like I
我开始打得很差
couldn't play tennis anymore.
然后感觉自己不会打网球了
And it just was it just felt like it
那一下感觉这件事
was a much bigger deal than just playing
突然远远不止是
a tennis match all of a sudden.
打一场网球比赛
We'll take one more.
最后一个问题
Madison, I appreciate this is straight
麦迪逊 我知道这是
after the match and you said you
刚打完就问 你刚说
might want to make some changes.
可能要做一些改变
I wonder are there changes
是不是有一些改变
that you've been thinking about making
你已经考虑了一段时间
and this maybe just pushes you towards
而这场球只是把你
them or is that more of a broad statement
往那儿推了一把 还是说
when you just think you don't want
只是一个笼统的说法
to feel like this anymore?
就是不想再有这种感觉了？
No, I think it's
不 我觉得这是
been something that's been building
一件积累了
for a while and I've I just kind
一段时间的事 我一直
of keep pushing it off
把它往后推
and pushing it off just because that's how
一推再推
the tennis world works
因为网球圈就是这样运转
and it's just to the point
现在已经到了
where I actually need to do something
我真的得做点什么
about it.
的时候了